A couple months ago, I interviewed one of
the most legendary business owners in the entire world.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah, what's up?
Question for you.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Uh, yeah.
And what do you do for a living out here
in Tampa to be able to afford a Rolls Royce?
I am a consultant.
Are you an entrepreneur?
I am definitely an entrepreneur.
I'm a business consultant.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Most amount of money I've
ever made in a single year?
$15 million.
$15 million?
Yeah.
Have you ever been broke before?
I was broke for the first part of my life.
Then I made millions of dollars.
And then I was broke again.
And now we've set it up in
such a way that that doesn't happen anymore.
Do you believe in God?
I more than believe in God.
I trust God.
That video got over 150 million views across social media.
That's Myron Golden.
And he invited us out to his private golf course out in Tampa, Florida to
give you guys the blueprint on how you can become a multimillionaire in today's world.
And how you can sell and market
like a $15 million a year entrepreneur.
This video is about to
be insane from start to finish.
So stay tuned until the end.
But with that being said,
let's get this video on the way.
All right, you guys.
So we made it to the
golf course out here in Tampa, Florida.
And Myron's going to be pulling up at any second.
So stay tuned because you're not
going to want to miss this.
My God, Myron's pulling up right now.
So we're going to wait for him to
come out and go up to him, you guys.
Come on.
There he is.
What's up?
How you doing, man?
Fantastic, brother.
It's great to see you.
Great to see you.
Thanks for having us out here, man.
It's great to see you again.
Great to see you.
Fancy meeting you here.
Yeah, absolutely.
We were letting them know how
many views our last video did.
It was crazy, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Do you know what the number is on Instagram?
No.
100 and something million.
100 billion.
Yeah, it's 100 and something million.
It's crazy.
Have you ever seen anything like that before?
Never.
Never?
I've never seen anything like it.
Yeah.
I've never seen.
I didn't even know videos got 100 million views.
But I like to say where attention goes, revenue flows.
What?
You like that one?
I do.
I know we're at the golf course.
We need to get a million dollars
for the game for them in this video.
Can we make it happen out there?
We can make that happen.
But before we do, I got to make
sure I take care of this young lady.
All right, brother.
Time to go.
Let's go.
It's time to bring the game to them.
I love it.
How long have you been a business owner?
47 years.
Growing up, did you know you were going
to be a business owner and build an empire?
Definitely not.
No, I didn't have any idea.
I learned, though, when I was 16
that you don't have to have a job.
Because my dad quit his job and he said
he was never going to work for anybody again.
I'm like, what are we going to do?
He just started doing for himself what he used to
do for other people and got to keep all the money.
How much money did you make this last year?
Eight figures.
We got to head to this next shot.
Yes, we do.
Let's go.
We do.
We're on a golf course right now.
Yep.
This is a playground for
a lot of millionaires and billionaires.
For real.
Yeah.
What do you notice about all the
billionaires and the wealthiest people that you've met?
What are the most successful
to do differently from everybody else?
Hyper-focus on intention and ignore distraction.
So you don't like diversifying.
You like focus going deep on one thing.
Well, diversifying is a different conversation.
I don't like distractions.
Intention is anything that moves the needle in your favor.
Distraction is anything that you focus on that
does not move the needle in your favor.
In terms of how wealthy people play with their
money, what do they do differently from everybody else?
Ask me that question when we get over to Tika.
We got to get out of these guys.
I got you.
So you were saying, what do the
wealthiest people do differently from everybody else?
I think they perceive life differently is number one.
But as a wealthy person, you don't view
the primary purpose of money as paying bills.
So poor people think the primary
purpose of money is paying bills.
Middle class people think the primary purpose of money is to maintain good credit so
they can buy things they can't afford to impress people they don't know or like.
Rich people believe the primary purpose of
money is to turn it into more money.
So that's like when I get a dollar,
I want to turn it into 10 or prefer.
I want to turn it into 100 or
even 1,000 before I spend any of that dollar.
The secret to being able to flip that money, to make that
money work for you, to double and multiply and grow that money.
Being able to perceive what's valuable to other people.
So it doesn't matter whether you're trading stocks or whether
you're investing in real estate or whether you're selling insurance.
It doesn't matter.
You have to solve somebody else's problem
in order to solve your money problem.
And you can't be focused on
your money problem when you're solving it.
You have to be focused on whatever their problem is.
How old were you when you made your first million?
I was 43.
No, I was 45.
I was 45 when I made my first million.
But you had lost it when you had.
Well, I didn't.
I had made a million dollars a year for a couple of years
in a row and then lost every, I mean, lost all my money.
Why did you lose everything?
We just had a whole series of tragedies.
Sometimes life comes at you fast.
And I upgraded my lifestyle way too
soon when I first started making money.
But when you first start making 30, 40,
50,000 a month, you think you're a big baller.
80,000 a month, 100,000 a month, you think, oh
man, we're making so much money, it'll never run out.
But the scripture says when riches
increase, so do they that consume them.
So when you start making more money,
you are going to have more expenses.
So what you have to do
is you have to make sure that.
You set yourself up in such a way that
you don't spend every dime out of every dollar.
You don't even, if you can live off of
10% of your revenue or 10% of your income,
now you're in a place where the bottom can fall out and
you're still going to be okay for at least a couple of years.
Yeah.
Right?
There's a saying that I love, stay small enough,
long enough, and you'll be big enough soon enough.
Ooh, that's a bar.
It's like even if you're making, like you said, 30,
40, $50,000 a month, it's like keep the expenses low.
Keep the expenses low.
Yeah.
Even when the margins and the profits are high.
Absolutely.
And it gives you the ability
to acquire massive amounts of wealth.
And the more money you have, if
you understand how to turn money into money.
The bigger that amount gets, the faster it gets bigger.
If you're not always taking
money out to go buy stuff.
And there's nothing wrong with buying stuff.
But you want to make sure
that the business is sustained first.
What industry would you get into right now?
Something to do with AI.
Really?
Oh, for sure.
Why?
Well, because it's easier to create wealth in the economic era that
you're living in than it is to create wealth in the past.
So every time wealth changes sectors or
categories, a new economic era is introduced.
From the beginning of time to the mid-1700s.
You had the agricultural age.
Land equaled wealth.
From the mid-1700s to the mid-1900s.
Industrial age.
Machines equaled wealth.
From 1955 to 1978, the distribution age.
Outlets equaled wealth.
And right now, we are in the AI age.
So the people who got started in AI
in 2020, 2021, 2022, and even today, 2025.
Those are the people who
create the wealth of the future.
If you had to start from zero and you had 90 days to
make a million dollars in your life, depending on it, what would you do?
I don't think like that because
I don't give myself deadlines like that.
So I think you may
already know this, but they don't.
I don't believe in setting goals.
A goal.
Is an objective with a deadline.
I don't control deadlines.
I don't control the times and seasons.
It's like saying to a farmer, okay, if you had to produce
7 million ears of corn by next Wednesday, what would you do?
Well, there's nothing you could do.
So instead of doing that, have an objective for inputs.
An objective for outcomes.
But don't put a time limit on it.
Because let it happen when it happens.
And that way you're not frustrating yourself by setting a
goal, not reaching the goal, and then feeling like a failure.
Because it didn't happen when you
thought it was going to happen.
Because it might happen two days later.
And you still felt like a failure for two days.
Or if it happens two years later, you
wasted time feeling like a failure for two years.
And that feeling like a failure for
two years might even cause you to quit.
Only objective applies.
Are you a good salesman?
Without sounding braggadocious, one of
the best in the world.
One of the best in the world.
So what's the one thing that you do differently from 99% of
other salesmen that's enabled you to become part of that top 1%?
I only sell people things they desire to buy.
So do you think a lot of people
that they sell bullshit that people don't need?
I would never phrase it like
that because I don't use profanity.
I think a lot of people want people
to buy stuff simply because they're selling it.
I only want people to buy
things that they already want to buy.
See, most people are looking for something.
They're looking for somebody to sell their
stuff to so they can make some money.
I believe that there are already millions of people in the world who would
love to buy what you'd love to sell if they only knew you existed.
So instead of trying to find somebody to
sell something to because you have something for sale,
make yourself findable for people who want
to buy what you already want to sell.
Make selling really easy.
Did you come from a rich family?
Do you mean rich in money?
Because the answer to that would be absolutely not.
No.
So how did you change your family's trajectory?
There's the saying that, you know, the
rich get richer, the poor get poorer.
How did you escape the cycle of poverty?
I think the rich get
richer and the poor get poorer.
But the poor don't get poorer.
The rich get richer and the rich
don't get richer because the poor get poorer.
Those statements are true, but they're not causality.
They're a correlation.
They're not causation.
How did I escape the cycle of poverty?
First of all, I hated being poor.
And then I learned the things that rich people did.
And I started doing those instead of
doing the things that poor people did.
What did you learn and implement into your skill set?
Number one, like my good friend
Daniel Priestley says, income follows assets.
So I stopped focusing on working hard.
I stopped focusing on eight
hours work for eight hours pay.
I stopped focusing on paying bills.
I started focusing on, okay, how can
I put more assets in my asset column?
Because income.
Follows assets.
So you bought a lot of assets.
I did.
I bought and built because you can
buy assets, but you can also build assets.
I've written books.
For instance, every book that I've written is an asset.
It pays me money every month.
So you write the book once, but it
pays you for the rest of your life.
That's an asset.
What are you investing in right now?
Real estate options, some crypto.
The most important thing I've ever invested in is
my own mind to learn the things I don't know.
So I can do the things I couldn't do before.
Have you spent a lot of money on mentorship?
Depends on your definition of a lot of money.
I haven't spent as nearly as much as I've made.
And how much money would you say?
You.
Spent on mentorship.
If you include all the books, all the
courses, all the coaching programs, all of it.
About 1.7 million.
1.7 million.
What's the greatest lesson you've learned from
investing over a million dollars into mentorship?
Mentorship is like the ultimate shortcut.
It's like somebody's already spent their whole
life figuring out how to do something.
And all they're going to do is charge you
up some money to teach you how to do it.
Sign me up for that program.
I remember my first mentor, Jerry.
He showed me how to sell to many,
like one on one to many from stage.
And the stuff he showed me was invaluable.
It was just like.
Wait, what?
I didn't even believe it would work, but I did
it because he was my coach and he said, do it.
And it worked so well that the first time I did it,
it was hard for me to keep from breaking out into hysterical laughter.
I'm like, this is crazy.
It's been here all along.
It's not just the things that we don't know.
It's the things that we don't know we don't know.
That's the problem.
What is the best advice
you ever received from a mentor?
I think the thing that changed my trajectory wasn't so much
a piece of advice as it was something that Robert G.
Allen, the author of Multiple Streams of
Income, said to me at a seminar.
He was asking for testimonies.
I told him, you know, I've read your book.
I've read your books and I've used some
of your material and some of your courses.
And, you know, I'm doing really good.
I used to be a
trash man making $6.25 an hour.
Now I'm living like a king.
I'm making $30,000 a month.
You know what he said to me?
He said, you're doing really good.
You're on the path to making some really big money.
And he said that to me
in front of like 700 people.
The first thought was, did he just diss
my $30,000 a month in front of 700 people?
My second thought was, wait, there's a level where
$30,000 a month is not a lot of money.
Oh, let me get to that level.
You have to think a
lot bigger is what you're saying.
You have to think a lot bigger and you
have to learn to perceive the big things that are
already there all around you so you can access them.
People think they lack access to abundance.
They don't like access to abundance.
They lack access to awareness
of abundance that's all around them.
You guys, that was an incredible answer from
Myron, but I needed to take a second real
quick to thank you guys for helping
us hit 1 million subscribers on YouTube.
You guys, this is an incredible milestone in our journey.
And since you guys helped me get to this
point, I have to give back to you guys.
And right now, this week, I'm going to
give you the opportunity to join my private
entrepreneur community.
The School of Mentoring.
This is the number one community for
business owners and people trying to self-improve in
the entire world.
And the reason why it's become the number
one community for business owners in the world
is because every single week I bring
in one of the multimillionaires and the billionaires
that I interview on this channel to directly
mentor you and answer all of your questions
on live Zoom calls every single week.
For example, Myron Golden, who we're interviewing right
now, he came in and he mentored our
community.
Guys, Myron made $15 million in a single year.
He taught our community step by step how to sell.
And how to market over a live call.
I've also had billionaires like Steven Klubeck, who
sold his company for $2.2 billion to Hilton.
He taught our company how to start their
business, how to get capital, how to get investment,
and how to grow and eventually sell a company.
You guys, this type of mentorship, you
cannot find anywhere else on the planet.
And since we hit a million subscribers for
this week only, you can join my community
at the lowest rate, the
lowest price it has ever been.
At $30 a month, you guys.
You cannot get mentored
from multimillionaires or billionaires.
You can get mentored from a multi-millionaire or
a billionaire every week at a more affordable
rate.
So come in and join the community.
Come in and get mentored
from a multi-millionaire or a billionaire.
But I want to go even beyond that.
For somebody that joins the community this week,
you will be entered in to win one of
these three prizes.
Starting with this, a free live
one-on-one call with a multiple eight-figure entrepreneur,
where you can ask your question to a
business owner whose business is doing multiple eight
figures a year.
I'm also going to be giving away free lifetime
access to one of the members that joined this
week.
You will get free live calls every
single week with the multimillionaires and the billionaires
that I interview on this channel.
And lastly, I'm going to be giving away a
free trip to one of the members that joined
this week to come and shoot content
with me and meet several multimillionaires and billionaires
in one of the next cities that I film in.
So you do not want to miss this opportunity
to join and become a member of the number
one community for business owners in the entire world.
All you have to do to join is go
down to the link in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you
on the inside of my community.
The School of Mentors.
But with that being said,
let's get back to the video.
So how can somebody get in the room
if they don't have a lot of credibility?
You pay to be in the room.
You buy your way into the room, right?
And you get paid on
the way out of the room.
I joined a mastermind 10 years ago, actually,
and I was the brokest person in that mastermind,
right?
I was just like, I talked him into letting
me do a special payment plan because I wanted
to be in the program.
And everybody in that mastermind acted like my
ideas were the best ideas they'd ever heard.
And so eventually what that caused me to realize
is I had been selling to the wrong people
my whole life.
I was selling to the people who needed
it instead of the people who wanted it.
That's one.
And then a lot of those people later
became my clients, even though I wasn't in there
sniping.
They just became my clients because they
wanted to learn the stuff I knew.
But I didn't even realize the
value of the stuff I knew.
I only thought people who came from where I
was coming from saw value in the stuff I
knew.
I didn't realize people who were way ahead
of me, like financially, would see value in
the ideas that I had.
And so learning to sell to the right
people, one of the most valuable things I've ever
done.
How do you identify the right
market to go into and sell to?
A lot of people, they get shiny object
syndrome where they say, oh, this and that.
How do you identify the right market?
How do you identify the right
market to go in and sell?
Well, it depends on what your objective is.
So one of the things I learned a long time
ago is if you want to get rich, sell to rich
people, right?
Sell to people with money.
Why?
Because they have the money to buy the stuff and
it's easy to get them to pay for it because
they have the money.
Okay, so cool.
When I think about the right people, I
make my messaging so that it attracts the right
people, repels the wrong people.
Like a lot of people, the last thing
they tell you when they're attempting to sell you
something is the price.
Because the stuff I sell,
my coaching is $40,000 an hour.
My mentorship programs, my masterminds,
they range from $20,000 to $30,000.
They're all free.
I can sell $27,000 all the way
up to a million dollars a year.
And so I put that out there up front.
So the people who I'm not for know I'm not
for them and they don't bother me and I don't
bother them.
Everybody's happy.
So you said you got to solve expensive
problems because would you agree that it's the same
stress to go after $5,000 problems as $100,000 problems?
Yeah, it requires the same level of
energy is how I would describe it.
It takes no more energy to sell
a million dollar program, million dollar offer than
it does to sell a thousand dollar offer.
You're just selling it to a different person.
If a person's ready to buy, they're
ready to buy what they're ready to buy.
So how do you get money from a rich person?
See, I don't see selling as getting money from people.
I see it as delivering value to them.
You get money from them because they
happily pay you because you've solved the problem
they've been struggling with for a long time.
How do you define sales?
I just find sales as uncovering the value of
what I have to offer so well that people
are happy to exchange the money they have
in their pocket for the value I've revealed.
So most people, they think of selling as
talking somebody into buying something you don't want,
don't need and can't afford, right?
Because they don't under, they don't
see selling the way I do.
If somebody says no to their offer, the
first thing they do is lower their price.
But I recommend instead of lowering your price.
Why don't you just raise the value, like
offer them more value and then people will
be happy to pay for it.
And what's the most amount of money
that you made in a single day?
Most amount I've ever made in a single
day, probably five and a half million dollars.
You made five million in a single day?
Yeah.
How?
Well, by making an offer to a group of
people, making a premium value offer to a group of
people.
So you just get the attention and then you just...
Right.
What you garner the attention over time, but
what you do is you develop a relationship.
Like if people are going to pay you
55,000, for instance, they have a relationship with
you generally on some level, at
least in their minds they do.
You don't walk up to a girl
and say, hi, my name is James.
Will you marry me?
Right?
If you ask her that, she's
going to be scared and say no.
She's not scared and say no,
you should be scared and run away.
You build that rapport and that trust over time.
Over time.
Yeah.
With people.
Like Frank Kern says, prove to people that
you can help them by actually helping them.
And so that's one of the things that
you do with your School of Hard Knocks channel.
That's one of the things
I do with my YouTube channel.
I prove to people that I
can help them by actually helping them.
People say in their comments on my YouTube
channel all the time, I can't believe this
guy does this much, gives
us this much value for free.
But it's not really free because they
have to pay for it with their attention.
And here's what I've discovered.
People pay you long enough with their
attention, they'll eventually pay you with their assets.
Wow.
Which means that they'll invest in you.
They'll invest in themselves through you.
Now, when I first interviewed you, I asked you
if you believed in God and you said, I
don't just believe in God.
I believe in God.
I trust God.
Yeah.
How did you find that trust in God?
Why do you trust God?
Because he's never lied to me.
But then again, he's never lied
to anyone because God cannot lie.
I trust God because he's proven to me
over and over and over again that everything he
says in his word, which I believe is the Bible.
It's not just true, but it's truth.
What's a financial lesson from the Bible
that a lot of people do not know?
Does God want people to be rich?
God wants some people to be rich
because God want everybody to be rich.
I don't think God has the same plan for everybody.
That's why everybody's a different person because
he's got a different purpose for everybody.
I do believe that it's God's design for his
children to be rich, but I believe that God
also has exceptions to his own rules.
And so some people, they have a different assignment.
Now I can't tell you whether or not God wants
you to be rich, but I can tell you there's
no doubt in my mind that
he wants me to be rich.
Because if he didn't.
He wouldn't have shown me
the principles that made me rich.
And so you say, what's a principle in
the Bible that can help people be rich?
Well, it says the blessing of the Lord, it
maketh rich and he addeth no sorrow with it.
He who will be greatest among
you, let him be servant of all.
One of the things I found out in business
is you can be great even if you're not good,
if you're willing to serve enough people,
because greatness is your ability to serve
the masses.
How old are you now?
I am 63.
I'll be 64 in two months.
What has God been teaching you in the last year?
Man, there's so much.
What has God been teaching me in the last year?
That life is short.
And even if you live
to be 100, life is short.
So love the people you love and don't
just repeat the same experience over and over.
Pack your life with life experiences.
Pack every day with life experiences.
Live every day with gratitude in your heart.
Greatest lesson?
Everything good in my life is a gift.
That's the greatest lesson.
I woke up this morning and I opened
my eyes and guess what I could do?
I could see.
And I know how to make myself look,
but I don't know how to make myself see.
You've got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate you letting us come out here.
This is excellent.
Where can everybody find you at?
You can find me on my website, MyronGolden.com.
Or on YouTube, Myron Golden.
Or if you want to follow up my
Bible study, Bible Study with Myron Golden on YouTube.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
This one was incredible.
Myron dropped so many gems for you guys.
So I need you guys to like and
subscribe for amazing content we've got coming every single
week because I'm going all over the
world to interview the most successful people in
the entire world for you.
As I mentioned earlier, if you are not
a member of my entrepreneur community, the School of
Mentors, the number one community for business
owners in the entire world, you are missing
out.
Because every single week inside of
this community, I bring in the multi-millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview to mentor you.
So if you want your life to change by
getting around the most successful people in the world,
come become a member and join the community today.
All you have to do is go down
to the link in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you
on the inside of the community.
With that being said, see you in the next video.